<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DYCard</string>
    <string name="logo">Logo</string>

    <!--Button-->
    <string name="buttonPrecedent">Back</string>
    <string name="buttonSuivant">Next</string>


    <!--Main Activity-->
    <string name="connexion">To log in</string>
    <string name="inscription">Sign in</string>
    <string name="connexionFacebook">Sign in with Facebook</string>
    <string name="cg">Term of use</string>

    <!--Inscription Activity-->
    <string name="pseudo">Username</string>
    <string name="mdp">Password</string>
    <string name="mdpConfirm">Retype password</string>
    <string name="email">E-mail</string>
    <string name="mdpDifferents">Passwords are different.</string>
    <string name="inscriptionSucces">Successful registration!</string>
    <string name="inscriptionEchec">The username or e-mail is already used.</string>


    <!--Connexion Activity-->
    <string name="erreurFormulaire">An error has occurred.</string>
    <string name="champsVides">Please fill in all fields.</string>
    <string name="erreurLogin">Connection error</string>
    <string name="connectionReussie">Successful connection!</string>
    <string name="erreur">Wrong login </string>
    <string name="mdp_oublie">Forgot your password</string>


    <!--Recup mdp Activity-->
    <string name="recupMdp">Password recovery</string>
    <string name="Valider">Confirm</string>


    <!--Etape1 Activity-->
    <string name="etape1_bienvenue">Welcome !</string>
    <string name="etape1_instructions">The steps to create your postcard : </string>
    <string name="etape1_instruction1">Choose the format for your postcard</string>
    <string name="etape1_instruction2">Choose the photo and format for your postcard
        The photo will cover the whole of your postcard
    </string>
    <string name="etape1_instruction3">Write your message on the back of the postcard</string>
    <string name="etape1_instruction4">Indicate this(these) recipient(s)
        Saving a recipient is possible
    </string>
    <string name="etape1_instruction5">Validate your order</string>
    <string name="etape1_instruction6">Pay</string>
    <string name="etape1_btn_creer">Create my postcard</string>
    <string name="etape1_enveloppe">*Your postcard will be sent in an envelope</string>



    <!--activity photo-->
    <string name="choisir_photo">Choose your photo</string>
    <string name="importerImage">Import photo</string>
    <string name="format">Choose the format of the postcard : </string>
    <string name="format1">Polaroid</string>
    <string name="format2">A6</string>
    <string name="format3">A4</string>

    <!--Alerte format-->
    <string name="alerteFormat">Please select a format</string>
    <string name="valider">OK</string>

    <!--Alerte photo-->
    <string name="alertePhoto">Please select a photo</string>
    <string name="oui">OK</string>

    <!--activity images-->
    <string name="choisir_forme">Choose your form</string>


    <!--Texte Activity-->
    <string name="ecris_ton_texte">Write your message</string>
    <string name="zoomer">Zoom in</string>
    <string name="dezoomer">Zoom out</string>


    <!--Destinataire Activity-->
    <string name="supprimer_destinataire">Delete this(these) recipient(s)</string>
    <string name="envoyer_ma_carte_ces_destinataires">Send </string>
    <string name="supprimer_ces_destinataires_de_mes_historiques">delete</string>

    <string name="prix_commande">The price for your order is :</string>
    <string name="envoyer_destinataires">Send my postcard</string>
    <string name="selectionne_les_destinataires">Select a recipient(s)</string>
    <string name="ajouter_nouveau_destinataire">Add a new recipient</string>
    <string name="chargementDest">Loading recipient...</string>


    <!--Ajout destinataire Activity-->
    <string name="buttonDestinataire">Add this recipient </string>
    <string name="nom">Last name</string>
    <string name="prenom">First name</string>
    <string name="adresse">Address</string>
    <string name="codepostal">Postal Code</string>
    <string name="ville">City</string>
    <string name="pays">Country</string>
    <string name="alerteDestinataire">Please fill in all fields</string>
    <string name="ajoutDestSucces">Recipient added </string>
    <string name="ajoutDestEchec">A recipient already exists for this address </string>
    <string name="ajout_destinataire">Add a recipient</string>



    <!--popup destinataire-->
    <string name="popupDestinataire">Please select at least one recipient</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>

    <string name="popupSupprimerDestinataire">Are you sure to delete this(these) recipient(s)?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>



    <!--validation-->
    <string name="validation">Validation</string>
    <string name="face_avant">Front of the postcard</string>
    <string name="face_arriere">Back of the postcard</string>
    <string name="parametres">Settings</string>
    <string name="destinataire">Recipient(s)</string>
    <string name="modifier">Edit</string>
    <string name="paiement">Payment method</string>

    <string name="erreurConnexion">Check your Internet connection</string>

    <string name="termsOfUse">
        Terms and Conditions of Use (TCU)

Preamble

DYCard is a company that distributes postcards mainly customizable online, as defined below.
Customer service:
3 Rue Des Blés d’or,
78180 Montigny-le-Bretonneux
France
E-mail: dycard.client.srv@gmail.com


Definitions and description of products and services:

“User”: means any natural or legal person using and commanding directly on Mobile Applications by any means such as telephone, tablets, hereinafter referred to as "the User".

"Application (s)": means the mobile application edited by DYCard.


"Product (s)": means the products offered on the day of the User\'s consultation on the Application: card shop products such as greeting cards, thank you cards, invitations, handouts, postcards and a whole range of objects and photo gifts, as well as accessory products such as envelopes, for example.
The User is informed that the Products present on the Application are as faithful as possible to those actually printed but may be slightly different (size, colors, etc.). Each product is accompanied by a description drawn up by DYCard directly.

"Service (s)": means the services proposed and described at the time of consultation and / or ordering on the Mobile Application including but not limited to: creating and customizing online Products for printing and shipping by DYCard, One of its subcontractors or suppliers as well as the associated services. These products and services are offered within the limit of available stocks.

Scope and object:

The purpose of these TCU is to govern the orders placed by the User on an Application. The User agrees to respect these TCU. The inscription on the Applications and / or the placing of an order expressly implies the full acceptance of these GCUs by these TCUs prevail on any other special or general conditions not expressly approved by DYCard. DYCard reserves the right to modify its TOU at any time. In this case, the applicable TCU will be those in effect on the date of registration and / or order by the User. If the User has already taken cognizance of TCU at the time of its registration, if DYCard will bring new general conditions to its knowledge later, the latter will prevail. These Terms and Conditions of Use may be downloaded and printed.



 Access and registration to services:

3.1 In order to use the Services, you must have access to the Internet (any charges for connection and use thereof are at the sole expense of the User). The User must have all the necessary hardware, including a Smartphone, a tablet or any other connection tool required by the Site or the Application, in order to ensure a sufficient connection to the Internet and Downloading of data, files and digital photographs in particular. The User must also have valid software and settings necessary for the proper functioning of the Services (eg updated internet browser, activation of Java script functions, acceptance of session cookies and acceptance of pop-up windows ").
Depending on the network configuration (behind a firewall or proxy), connection to the sites may not be possible.

3.2 Most Services require registration and account creation. The registration procedure is described on the Application. The User is solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of his email address and password and of any actions that may be carried out under your account and / or his password or email address. The User agrees to immediately inform DYCard, in writing (mail to customer service dycard.client.srv@gmail.com or mail at 3 rue des blés d\'or 78180 Montigny-le-Bretonneux), any unauthorized use Account and / or password and / or any breach of security and disconnect from his / her account, especially if using a public connection tool. DYCard shall not be liable for any loss or damage arising in the event of failure to comply with this paragraph.

Validation of Orders

4.1 The User who wishes to order must: be identified or register on the Site and / or fill in the mandatory fields requested in order to order on the Site or the Application. Validate its order after having verified all the elements; Make the payment as provided; Confirm its order and payment.

4.2 Any order received by DYCard is deemed to be firm and definitive and shall constitute an order upon confirmation of the order. The validation of the order is carried out: upon validation of the payment in case of payment by any secure online payment available on the Application such as Credit Card, Paypal. The confirmation of the order is practically simultaneous from the validation of the transaction by said payment means.
The validation of the order constitutes the agreement of the User on the characteristics of the sale (price, quantity, nature and format of the Products and Services, addresses). No modification or cancellation of order can take place from this validation unless exceptional agreement of DYCard.
4.3 The User is able to verify his order before validating it. DYCard declines all responsibility in the event of errors or forgetfulness on the part of the User: subject to the article 4.4 below as listed here non-limitatively: spelling, punctuation, grammar, resolution of downloaded images, dates, Address, quantity, format, selected options and any damage to products that occurred after delivery.
The User is informed and agrees to accept that the time limits run only from the validation of the order subject to the complete payment of the price of the order by the User. The transfer of ownership is carried out as of the validation of the order.

4.4 An option called "Tranquility" can be proposed by DYCard to the User before validation of his order on the Site. Notwithstanding the stipulations of article 4.3, in case of subscription by the User before validation of order, DYCard will check the electronic file of the customer’s visual before transmission for printing within a reasonable time. This option includes:
- Verification and correction of orthographic elements and syntax in French except personal data (such as but not limited to surnames, forenames, coordinates, dates, ages, weights, etc.) and, more generally, Be reasonably verified by DYCard
- Verification and possible correction of the layout of the visual
- Verification of the colorimetric rendering on the visual of the photos downloaded by the User on the card.
- Verification of the consistency of postal delivery addresses in metropolitan France.
DYCard reserves the right to correct certain elements directly and to validate the order of the User or to issue his reservations directly to the User by email. The User acknowledges to accept that the processing times of his order indicated on the website can be modified in case of subscription of this option, notably but not limiting, with respect to the period of return of the User in response to the reservations issued By the User, to the technicality and the time dedicated by DYCard to the correction of the Card of the User. DYCard undertakes to do everything possible so that the delays of processing of the Order of the User remain reasonable.
DYCard reserves the right to initiate the validation and printing of the User\'s card, in the absence of a reply from the User within 3 working days from the sending of the reservations mail to the User.

Absence of right of withdrawal

The User is informed that, in accordance with applicable and applicable legal and / or regulatory provisions, he / she will not be entitled, from the date of issue by DYCard of the Service and the Product, of the 14-day period starting on the date Acceptance of the offer and allowing the Service and the Product to be waived insofar as it recognizes and accepts that DYCard\'s provision of the Service and / or the Product is made before the end of this 14-day period And / or that the Products offered by DYCard are customized and / or made on demand.

Price

6.1 The price is due on order. The rates in effect are those displayed on the Application. The prices are expressed all taxes included taking into account in particular the VAT applicable on the day of the order; Any change in the rate may be reflected in the price of the goods or services.
DYCard reserves the right to modify its prices at any time, provided however that the price appearing on the site on the day of the order will be the only one applicable to the User.

6.2 Prices shall be independent of billing related to subscriptions and the telecommunication contract for Internet connection and the User shall deal personally with the negotiation of tariffs relating in particular to the telecommunication networks and services necessary for the use of the Internet.

6.3 When the User orders to be delivered outside Metropolitan France, the User may be subject to import duties and taxes, which are collected when the Products arrive at their destination. Any additional customs clearance fees will be borne by the User and DYCard has no control over these charges. DYCard advises the User to contact the local customs office for further information. Moreover, the User is considered as the official importer and undertakes to comply with all laws and regulations in force in the country of the delivery address.

Payment

7.1 Payments shall be made by the means of payment proposed when paying for the order on the Application. For credit card payments, credit card details are not kept. Payment is made directly to the bank. The order validated by the User is considered effective only when the payment centers concerned have given their agreement. If these centers are refused, the order is automatically canceled and the User is obligated to renew the order at a later date.

7.2 In order to benefit from the Paypal payment method, the User must have an account with PayPal. In case of payment by PayPal, it is the terms and conditions of use of Paypal that apply to consult on their website. In the event of cancellation of a deferred payment following a request from the User without valid reason, DYCard reserves the right to cancel the order or to demand the payment of the order from the User. Paypal claims and disputes will be settled according to the Paypal procedure

Default of Payment

In the event of non-payment, the User can not assert the right of ownership of the order or demand the respect of any DYCard reserves the right to refuse to make a delivery or to honor an order emanating from a Consumer who has not fully or partially settled a previous order or with whom a payment dispute is being administered.

Terms and time of manufacture and delivery

9.1 These delays may be postponed in the event of force majeure, including but not limited to transport strikes, strike by postal services, breakdowns, computer problems, exceptional stock-outs, etc.; Reservations issued by the quality service in the event of verification of the control or nonconformity of the control elements.

9.2 Delivery of products is foreseen in the list of countries proposed on the Sites or Applications when placing the order. The orders will be delivered to the destination address indicated in the order, by the delivery method indicated on the Site or Application.

9.3 Delivery times are those indicated on the Sites and Applications when placing the order. In case of exceeding by more than 7 days of the deadline (except force majeure or error of the User) of delivery, the User can cancel the order by addressing to DYCard a mail with request for advice of delivery. If the delivery did not take place or if the Service was not provided between the sending and receiving of the mail or this letter, the User may resolve the contract. DYCard will then have to refund all the sums paid by the User as soon as possible, and at the latest within 14 days of the resolution of the sale. Beyond these 30 days, DYCard must pay interest on the amount due. These interests are calculated in relation to the legal rate in force. However, delay in delivery can not give rise to any compensation, cancellation of the Order in progress or reimbursement of the latter, if it is established that the delay was caused by the fact of the Customer or consignee of the parcel or a third party and in cases of force majeure such as those referred to in the case law.
A new deadline is likely to run under the following assumptions:
- The Product is the subject of a re-edition at the initiative of the quality control.
- The Product is subject to modification or re-edition at the request of the User.
Failure to comply with the deadlines set out in this article due to fault or error attributable to the User or failure to comply with his obligations shall not entitle him to claim for reimbursement.
Any error or omission in the delivery address provided by the User and leading to the failure to send the order will be borne financially by the User subject to the provisions of Article 4.4.

9.4 In case of incomplete address, wrong address, refusal of the package by the recipient or lack of information resulting in an inability to deliver the product to the recipient in due time, DYCard can not be held responsible for the quality Delivery. If this lack of information results in a second presentation to the recipient, DYCard will be entitled to ask the customer for the costs corresponding to this second delivery.
Delivery by Chronopost (PROVINCE and REGION PARISIENNE): the deliverer will leave a notice of passage in the mailbox of the recipient or by sms if the User has communicated a mobile phone number valid at the time of the order. The latter will have to give instructions or come to withdraw it at the address specified on the notice of passage.
Delivery by La Poste (Colissimo followed or priority letter not followed): La Poste will be able to deliver the parcel to the caretaker, receptionist, neighbor, post office closest to the delivery address indicated at the time of the order Or in the delivery instructions.
The User agrees to accept these terms of delivery.
The delivery of the order to a third party (neighborhood, reception, caretaker, or post office of the recipient), according to the procedures of the carrier, does not require the express authorization of the final recipient.

 Claims - 100% Satisfied Guarantee

10.1 In spite of all the attention that DYCard devotes to satisfying the expectations of its Users, the Products that are delivered do not meet the legitimate expectations of quality and service for which DYCard has not explicitly defined exclusions as to its responsibility Under the terms of these User Terms, the User may assert a claim.

10.2 It is explicitly recalled that DYCard can not favorably receive any complaint concerning the personalization elements freely added to the articles customizable by the User or the address of delivery specified by the User.

10.3 It is the User\'s responsibility to ensure the quality of his photos and images as well as the predictable rendering of the Products ordered according to the chosen format but also their resolution. DYCard does not undertake any service for editing or modifying the photos and / or images provided by the User. It is up to the User to check the rendering of his Product before the validation of his order.

10.4 The User must present any complaint to our customer service, by email, specifying his pseudo, the reason of his claim and the evidence (photograph for example in case of qualitative problem, or delivery note in case of no Compliance with deadlines ...).

10.5 In accordance with the "satisfied or refunded" commitment, justified claims will give rise, at the customer\'s choice, to the realization of the new Services and a new delivery to DYCard if this is feasible, both for printing and Or a refund of the original order within a maximum of 4 weeks from receipt of proof of claim if the Product and / or Service can not be replaced.
DYCard reserves the right to demand the return of all Products, the return costs remaining the responsibility of the User.

 Force majeure

DYCard can not be held responsible in case of force majeure, means of transport and / or communication which would delay the execution of the services and the delivery of the products as listed without delay: delay, disruption or strike of the postal services, Means of transport and / or communication, computer breakdowns.

 Liability

12.1 The User is informed that the Products may be sent to unwanted recipients if the address indicated on the order is not correct or in the event of an exceptional error on the part of DYCard. In this case, DYCard can not be held responsible if the Products are sent in error to a third party who was not the intended recipient of the User.

12.2 The Services are reserved for strictly private use unless expressly agreed by DYCard. The User undertakes therefore to send only files of amateur photographic works, by definition without market value, and therefore not intended for commercial purposes or lucrative unless express agreement of DYCard.

12.3 DYCard shall not be held liable for any unauthorized or unauthorized use of the Services, in particular if the User sends an excessive amount of cards to the recipients or offensive, defamatory language.

12.4 DYCard shall not be held liable for any indirect damage suffered by the user during the supply of the Products or the use of the Services. The parties acknowledge that any indirect prejudice, any moral, commercial or financial damage as well as any action directed against the User by a third party are considered as non-exhaustive.
The User agrees to reimburse and / or indemnify DYCard for any claim, complaint or conviction of which DYCard is the object due to the non-respect of the present GCU and / or the messages transmitted via the Services. DYCard reserves the right at any time to modify or interrupt temporarily or permanently all or part of the Services without having to inform the Users beforehand and to close their user accounts. DYCard shall not be liable to Users or any third party for any modification, suspension or interruption of the Services. The quality of photo prints depends on the hardware and the cameras used. The User accepts that the rendering of the photos and / or images on the Products is less clear than on its screen. DYCard cannot be held responsible for the poor quality of the printing of the picture and / or picture due to poor quality or insufficient resolution of the photo and / or image downloaded as part of the Services.

 Compliance with a content charter

The User is reminded that the personalized creations transmitted within the framework of the Services belong to the private correspondence. DYCard therefore does not control or monitor these creations except for possible quality control if this is foreseen. As such, parents are encouraged to monitor the use of the Services by their minor children. The User is expressly informed that the files stored, used and transmitted within the framework of the Services are under his sole responsibility. Therefore, only the User of the Services will assume the civil as well as the criminal responsibility for the contents transmitted via the Services. However, DYCard alerts the User to the need to comply with the laws and regulations in force concerning the use of the Services. The User is prohibited from storing, downloading or sending any data that is prohibited, unlawful, unlawful, contrary to morality, decency, or public order and that infringes or is likely to infringe the rights of third parties. DYCard cannot be held responsible for the illegal nature of the photos and / or messages under the laws and regulations in force. The User is therefore prohibited from storing, uploading or transmitting any photographs and / or messages which could constitute incitement to the commission of crimes and offenses, provocation to discrimination, hatred or violence due to Race, ethnicity or nation, apology for Nazism, disputes over the existence of crimes against humanity, infringement of the authority of justice, information on Or an individual tax situation, of dissemination outside the authorized conditions of polling and simulation of voting relating to an election or referendum, defamation and insult, invasion of privacy, or In danger of the minors, as well as any file intended to exhibit objects and / or prohibited works, this enumeration not being limiting.
The User undertakes to comply with all the laws and regulations in force concerning the prohibition of the diffusion of pornographic images, obscene, or likely to seriously undermine the human dignity.
The User declares to be the legal owner of all the photos and files used in the Services and that they are free of all rights. The User may not register or transmit files that infringe the property rights of other persons, such as text, images, trade secrets, internal or confidential information, this list is not exhaustive.
The User may not record or transmit photographs or information that reveal the private or personal affairs of any person without his prior express consent. The User agrees that each person represented agrees to the use and the diffusion of his image.
The legal and regulatory provisions in force in France at the time of the order protect the contents made available to the User. Any total or partial reproduction must first be the subject of a prior written agreement of the publishers of each proposed content. Only the single reproduction is authorized for the strictly private use of the User. Any other reproduction, distribution, transmission or publication without the prior consent of the copyright holders
In the case of private correspondence, the User is expressly informed that DYCard does not control or monitor the files transmitted in connection with the use of the Service. However, the User acknowledges being informed that if DYCard is alerted by a third party or by any means whatsoever of the illegal nature of a content transmitted via the Services, DYCard will deliver the said contents to the law enforcement authorities who will process them Consequently. DYCard reserves the right, after having been seized by a judicial authority, to terminate access to the Services of the User issuing the disputed contents.

 Nominative data and cookies

14.1 The User acknowledges being informed that DYCard is systematically storing the images and photos uploaded by the User as well as its creation. The User can not, however, claim any minimum period of conservation of these. DYCard takes all necessary care to archive the information concerning the User in a secure environment. DYCard is authorized to register and use, by computer processing, the information provided by the User.

14.2 The User expressly undertakes to provide DYCard with sincere and genuine information concerning him. This information, transmitted within the framework of the orders, is indeed necessary for the processing, the sending and the follow-up of the orders.

14.3 DYCard or one of its partners may send postal or electronic mail to any person who provided his contact information. The third party prospecting mails will only be sent in case of agreement of the User. The User may at any time refuse to receive these offers. It shall be the User\'s responsibility to notify DYCard in writing by email to Customer Service.

14.4 DYCard may use cookies to store information identifying the User during the consultation of the Application in order to avoid having to enter them manually on each page consulted. In addition, these cookies are necessary for DYCard to provide the Services subscribed by the User. However, the User has the possibility to prevent the use of cookies by modifying the options of his software of navigation on the Internet.

14.5 The User is informed that the processing of the personal information communicated to DYCard was the subject of a declaration to the CNIL on May 9, 2005 under number 1092856. In accordance with the provisions of Law No. 78-17 of January 6 1978, any person who has provided data concerning him has a right of access, modification, rectification and deletion of all such data. For the exercise of one or more of these rights, it will be necessary to send the request by attaching a copy of his identity card
- By e-mail to: dycard.client.srv@gmail.com
- By post at: 3 rue des blés d\'or, 78180 Montigny-le-Bretonneux
Personal information collected by DYCard from the User may include name, surname, postal and / or electronic address, photographs, photographs and / or use of the Service (s).

 Other information concerning the User

15.1 In addition, certain non-personal information may be collected, such as the browser version of the member or any user (Firefox, Internet Explorer, etc.), the type of operating system used (Windows, Mac OS, etc.) The IP address of the computer being used.

15.2 Upon the User installing, downloading, logging in or using any of the mobile applications, smartphones, mobile website, via a third party platform such as Facebook, or any other social network ("our Virtual Services"), User authorizes DYCard to access and / or collect certain information retrieved via said third platform from its profile and / or its account in said third Platform or cookies and other technologies placed on its navigation software, hard drive, or In accordance with the contractual provisions and the confidentiality and security parameters established between the User and the said third Platform. The User authorizes DYCard to share this information with the said Third Platform in accordance with the contractual provisions and with your confidentiality and security parameters established between the User and the said Third Platform.
The User authorizes DYCard to possibly share, some of the information concerning him / her (eg behavioural and traffic data) collected from the User via the use, installation, connection to Virtual Services, with sub-¬ Contractors, partners, service providers and DYCards, located within or outside the European Union of DYCard, within the framework of the proper execution of the tasks entrusted to them by DYCard, the realization of services, optimization of DYCard performance, And / or for analytical purposes (enabling DYCard to improve the User\'s Services and experience, analyse the audience), and / or targeted advertising, which may require collection, preservation, reproduction , Use, or disclosure of any information about the User. Before any communication, the User\'s data will be anonymised so that they cannot be identified.

 Comments sent to the Site

Any feedback, suggestions, suggestions or other comments (collectively, "Comments") sent to DYCard in connection with the operation or Content of the Application will be provided by the Issuer and received by DYCard on a non-confidential basis. All such comments, suggestions and other information will become the exclusive property of DYCard. By submitting any such information to DYCard, the Issuer agrees to transfer and give, free of charge, all of its rights, title and interest in and to the information, including all copyrights and other intellectual property rights. The User agrees that DYCard may be free to use such information in a non-restrictive manner.

 Links to third party sites

Applications may present, or third parties may include from the Applications, links to other websites. (Mobile sites or third-party applications, social networks, etc.) DYCard cannot control the content of these sites. All access to these sites is under the sole responsibility of the User and at his own risk. DYCard can not be held liable for consequential losses or damages in connection with the User\'s use of these sites and can not be held responsible for their contents, advertisements, products, functionalities services or any other element Available on or from such third party websites which have not been previously and effectively identified as manifestly unlawful, by means of a notification in accordance with the laws and regulations in force.

 Protection of Mobile Applications

Intellectual and industrial property law protects all content of the Applications. The "DYCard" trademark is a registered and protected trademark and can not be used by third parties not affiliated with DYCard. The User may print or download images or parts of images from different areas of the Site exclusively for your own use and for non-commercial purposes. Any other form of duplication, redistribution, retransmission or publication of any downloaded image is prohibited without the express consent of DYCard, and the offender is liable to prosecution. You agree not to modify or remove the brands included in the downloaded images of the application.

 Jurisdiction

19.1 This contract is governed by French law.

19.2 In the event of a dispute, DYCard undertakes to make its best efforts to find an amicable solution. In the absence of an amicable solution, any dispute that may result from the interpretation of these General Conditions and / or the execution of the sales subject to it, will be the competence of the court of the defendant. If the User is a consumer, within the meaning of the law, he may, if he takes legal action against DYCard, choose the jurisdiction of the place of actual delivery of his order, in accordance with current legal provisions.

 Other

Any complaints should be sent by email. A Customer Service is at the disposal of the users:
- By email: dycard.client.srv@gmail.com
- By post: 3 rue des blés dor,\ 78180 Montigny-le-Bretonneux FRANCE

Any reproduction of these TCU, except for personal use, is prohibited.
Terms and conditions updated on 01/25/2017

    </string>


</resources>
